[music]
[müzik]
Someone sank to the bottom
Birisi dibe battı
But nobody cares
Ama kimse umursamıyor
We grieved, but tomorrow we forgot, as if we never were And we didn't love
Üzüldük, ama yarın unuttuk, sanki hiç olmamış gibi Ve sevmedik
Someone got lost in an endless dream That is, disappeared
Birisi uçsuz bucaksız bir hayale daldı Yani gitti
[music]
[müzik]
With a cold dawn, a new day rises upon us Everything will remain in this Universe
Soğuk bir şafakla yeni bir gün bize doğuyor Her şey bu Evrende kalacak
It returns to us, creating circles on the water Nothing passes without a trace, nothing
Bize geri dönüyor, suyun üstünde halkalar oluşturarak Hiçbir şey iz bırakmadan geçmiyor, hiçbir şey
Whose is this? A random move, a fatal turn? We touched each other on this spiral We found and lost again
Bu kime ait? Tesadüfi bir hamle, kaderi değiştirir mi? Bu spiralde birbirimize dokunduk Kazandık ve yeniden kaybettik
And we remain In a cold city, just waiting for it to get warmer, and run, regret nothing
Ve biz burada kalıyoruz Soğuk bir şehirde, sadece bekliyoruz, sıcaklaşırken Ve koşuyoruz, pişmanlık duymadan
It returns to us, launching hands Nothing passes without anything
Bize geri dönüyor, elleriyle halkalar oluşturarak Hiçbir şey iz bırakmadan geçmiyor, hiçbir şey
[music]
[müzik]
Moment, moment of revelation, mystery, enigma, Touch of God, union of delight and Fear I tried so many times, but in this very moment, my stone flies into the water
An, açığa çıkma anı, gizem, muamma, Tanrı'nın dokunuşu, hayranlık ve Korku Defalarca denedim, ama bu anım, taşım su üstüne atılıyor
And yet it always lands at the center of the circle I tried to throw it to the south, to the west, at sunset, in the morning With different angles, with stones of different types With my other hand, in a blind jump Some trap, but I still end up at the center of the circle
Ve her zaman dairenin merkezine düşer Güneye, batıya, gün batımında atmak için çabaladım, sabah Farklı açılardan, farklı taşlarla Bir elimle, kör bir sıçrayışta Bir tür tuzak, yine de dairenin merkezine düşerim
Year after year Nothing happens
Her yıl Hiçbir şey olmuyor
[applause]
[alkışlar]
Everything revolves It returns like this, launching
Her şey dönüyor Bize geri dönüyor, elleriyle halkalar oluşturarak
Nothing passes without a trace
Hiçbir şey iz bırakmadan geçmiyor
[music]
[müzik]